EXTRATERRESTRIAL
-Don't shout.
Sorry, sorry.
-I'll get dressed, okay?
-Okay.
Hey...
What?
Do you know where my pants are?
In the living room.
NO SIGNAL
Last night everything
fell out of my pocket
and I'm missing a two euro coin.
It's only two euros.
You can pay next time.
Don't worry about it.
Here.
Anyway...
Can I have some coffee?
It's burning.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I'm sorry but something urgent
came up...
Do you mind if I make a call?
There's something wrong with my cell,
there's no coverage.
This isn't working either.
Hold on.
Mine has no coverage either.
What time does yours say?
-Just past 7:30.
-Just past 7:30?
Yeah, the day got away from us.
Listen, I really need to be alone.
I'm sorry.
No one around, at this time?
Even on a Sunday...
Has something happened?
Did you hear anything?
None of the channels are working.
It's been like that since I got up.
What about the internet?
...in a state of emergency.
Please stay calm
and remain in your homes
until emergency crews arrive.
Contact them and follow
their instructions. Thank you.
Holy shit! What is that?
A temporary evacuation is underway...
There, out back.
-Got any binoculars?
-No.
...until emergency crews arrive.
The camera...
This is a message
from the Department of Defense.
-This is the zoom, right?
-Yeah.
How big is it?
Look, it's turning very slowly.
Yeah.
I think I can figure it out.
If I time how long it takes to turn
I can work out its size.
Got a calculator?
Yeah, you want it?
Yes, please.
Hey, excuse me...
-Julio.
-Oh, I'm Julia.
What a coincidence.
I don't know why I thought
your name was Luisa.
After last night no wonder
I can't remember...
By the way, where did we meet?
Hey, aren't you worried
about anybody?
I guess I should call my family,
they're all in Badajoz.
If the phones are working later.
You must have somewhere to go.
Yeah.
Yeah, my apartment.
I live in Hortaleza.
I'm renting a room
from some friends of my parents.
I can leave if you want.
No, wait till I find the calculator.
Should I leave after that?
No...
Sorry, what was the calculator
for again?
There's somebody there.
Hi.
-Angel.
-Hi.
This is...
What was your name again?
Julio.
I'm Julia, what a coincidence.
He's a friend...
I think you were right
to stay home.
People were so quick to take off.
Where could be better than right here?
Wow.
Is there anyone else
left in the building?
Actually, I don't know.
Trucks showed up around nine
with the military and they organized
the cars into lines.
I think everyone left but...
I don't really know
because I didn't open the door.
I watched TV all day
until it stopped working.
Is your internet working?
What have you been doing all day?
Didn't you hear me ringing?
Where did they take everyone?
I don't know, the suburbs,
the mountains...
Not far, because
there are more there.
More what?
More ships.
Don't you know what's going on?
Angel, is your internet working?
Worldwide they don't know,
but in Spain
more than 30 have appeared.
Especially over the cities.
Have you been in bed all day?
I tried ringing the bell...
How did you know she was here?
What?
Why didn't you think
she'd left with the others?
Because Julia always parks her car
in front of mine.
And it was there this morning,
that's how.
But you said you didn't go outside.
How did you see it?
From the window?
Yes.
No.
My internet isn't working.
No...
Anyway...
I'm going...
to the bathroom.
No, I'm leaving.
I'll call you later, Julia.
I think it's almost...
four miles wide.
Nobody's seen anything coming out,
right?
Well,
I think they come down from the middle.
That's why we can't see them from here.
What's up with your neighbor?
Is he always so transparent?
What?
It's obvious he stayed
because he saw your car
and knew you hadn't left, right?
How do you know
about all this stuff?
I'm an industrial designer.
Actually, I haven't finished my degree,
but I work making signs,
drawings, models...
I'm working on something amazing.
Some friends of my parents...
Well, the ones I'm renting from...
They're going to be in a parade
in their neighborhood
and they asked me to make this.
It's a float, something like this.
Well, more or less, okay?
And they want a car to pull the float,
but what I did was put the car
inside it.
Sorry, I'm really tired.
I'm going to bed.
See you tomorrow.
It's okay, it's me.
-What's wrong? What time is it?
-It's late, almost morning.
I was looking at the ship
and I thought, shit.
Anything can happen anytime.
Yeah.
I thought we could take turns
keeping watch.
Don't worry, I'll go first, okay?
But what happened?
No, it's just in case.
I'll wake you up
if something happens, okay?
-Where are you going?
-The living room, stay there.
No, I'm not sleepy.
-Quick, get up.
-What's going on?
-Are they attacking?
-Get washed.
Carlos!
Julia.
Where have you been?
They were taking people
to El Escorial...
Sweetheart, I'm so glad you're here.
They were taking people to El Escorial
and you weren't there...
but there were people
from this neighborhood.
I called and you didn't answer.
And since you had gone out...
By the way, I'm not alone.
Hi.
Carlos, this is...
-Sorry, what was your name?
-Julio.
What a coincidence!
Like me.
-Hi, Julio.
-Hi.
Feeling any better?
Yeah.
You're lucky Julia saw you
from the window. If you'd blacked out
one street up nobody'd have seen you.
-I almost did last night.
-What happened?
I walked here from El Escorial.
Eight and a half hours.
It got dark at Ciudad Universitaria.
I spent the night in a tent
until some jerks woke me up
screaming like crazy all night
and breaking windows.
Nothing happened
but it was scary.
What's this?
Did you draw it?
Yeah, I'm a designer.
Have a seat.
Julio was drawing
what he saw outside for me.
It's good. Damn, it's spot on.
I know people who've seen it
closer up and showed me photos
but you can't see shit.
What's that?
Holy shit!
I heard about a weird car
driving around.
It sounded like
a military vehicle,
but this is something else.
This is serious, damn it!
Where did you see it?
Out there.
Here? On this street?
I didn't see anything.
This is...
I saw it.
It drove right past.
I described it
and this looks a lot like it.
Nice going, Julio.
-Good work.
-Thanks.
-Shit, you could have told me...
-I know, I'm sorry.
I'd have left right away
and saved you the trouble.
I put my foot in it.
I don't know what to say.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving.
You're leaving?
I'm in the way.
No, you're not.
With all the mayhem out there...
You might black out again.
Come inside.
Angel stayed behind too.
You don't say.
We can't get rid of that guy,
not even with UFOs. Come in.
Hi, Angel.
Come by for dinner later!
The military has fenced off the area
right under the ship.
Apparently people have seen
some crazy stuff out there.
Anyway,
besides that weird tank Julia saw
I don't believe any of it.
You saw a weird tank?
Yeah, I have a drawing of it
in there.
If they brought huge ships all this way
there must be a reason, right?
They'll do something.
Maybe...
Look, I don't mean to scare you,
but I overheard two cops talking
at a highway checkpoint
and it's been on my mind
ever since.
Maybe they're already doing something
but in a way that we don't realize.
I think...
Maybe they're invisible.
Maybe they can fit in among us
without us noticing.
But shouldn't we leave?
There are ships everywhere.
I think...
At least we're someplace
we can control.
Well, I think that's pretty lame.
They come here in flying devices
bigger than towns
and suddenly they're worried about
being noticed? It makes no sense.
What do you think then?
Let's hear it.
I think they're testing humans
to see what we're like,
how we react,
if we're intelligent,
if we're brave...
They're probably
watching us and all the people fleeing
are making fools of themselves
because there's no need.
I'll pass.
Then those of us staying home
are doing the right thing.
We'll get a prize.
You'll get a prize.
Carlos, help me with this.
-No, they're here to stalk us.
-I hope not.
Because our neighbor
has that covered.
-Carlos.
-I'm coming.
Get the peaches I brought,
they're tasty.
I put them in the fridge.
What?
What's the problem?
What do you mean?
No, what's wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong with me.
What's with that face?
What's with what face?
Come on, I can tell.
You can tell what?
That you're jealous.
Jealous of what?
You can tell I'm jealous of what?
That you're into her
and you haven't screwed her.
Oh, yeah?
And why should I be jealous?
You know exactly why.
You must have heard us fucking
or something.
Don't give me that look
like you didn't know.
You knew, stop pretending.
You didn't know?
Try to open this.
My hands are wet.
Let me see if I can...
We're short on food.
We can check
the neighbors' apartments.
I think the supermarket
out back stayed open.
In the worst case we can plant
something on the terrace.
What do you think, Angel?
Should we plant lettuce?
Maybe the spacemen
will give us diplomas.
Carlos...
Shit!
Damn.
-It's nothing.
-Are you sure?
Damn it!
I'm really sorry.
Does it hurt?
Next time aim the other way
and hold it tighter.
I can't stand that guy.
Sometimes I wish he'd fuck her to see
if he'd calm down and leave us alone.
Julia?
Hard to believe I thought
he was a snooty homo at first.
But you can totally tell
he's into Julia.
You can tell, you can tell...
Angel, nothing happened!
Don't make things up!
Nothing happened!
Thanks for dinner.
See you tomorrow.
I'm going to bed too.
Wake up!
Is it my turn?
No more turns. You're leaving.
Leaving? Why am I leaving?
How could you tell Angel that?
How dare you!
What did I tell him?
You know exactly what you told him.
No, I don't.
You and I never had sex, okay?
I know we didn't.
What are you talking about?
Hypocrite.
You're lecturing me on sincerity?
You of all people.
Where will I go?
It's cold.
Let me eat something first,
I'm hungry.
Here.
Really, Julia, I didn't say anything.
Maybe I said something
and he understood whatever he wanted.
Who cares anyway?
You don't know him.
He's lost his mind.
Well, he'll get over it.
Last night he said
if I don't tell him, he will.
Shit.
Come to my place if you want.
Wait, wait!
Just one thing and I'll leave.
But please, listen to me.
You win, asshole!
Julio...
I went to the supermarket.
The one you said.
Why did you go by yourself?
Come in.
What the fuck are you doing?
-It doesn't fit.
-What doesn't?
Angel. He said he never left
his apartment,
but he knew your car was parked
in front of his, right?
Yeah, so what?
It turns out his car
is the one that isn't there.
You mean it was stolen?
Who'd steal that crate?
At least parked next to yours...
What are the chances everybody
would leave the building except him?
Telling us some crazy story
and watching us the whole time...
And the strangest thing...
What scares me the most...
What?
I swear to God I didn't tell him
anything about us.
What do you mean?
There's something strange about Angel,
we can't trust him
and I think Carlos should know
right away.
Julio! You didn't bring
an extension lead, did you?
What?
Did you see how he reacted
to what you said last night?
About them being among us?
He freaked out.
Okay, are you guys telling me
there's a chance
the Angel next door
isn't the Angel we know?
I don't know him at all,
but he seems very weird to me,
a troublemaker.
I don't know about you guys...
What did he say to you last night?
At dinner,
when you two were alone.
Before he took off all of a sudden.
He said something to you.
It's been troubling you ever since.
That you've been acting strangely.
That there's something odd
about you.
I said I didn't believe him,
of course.
That's why he took off like that.
Look, it's unlikely this Angel
is not the real Angel...
but we can't take any chances.
Hey, what's up?
Hi.
Did you take the peaches
with you last night?
No, I left them here.
I don't see them anywhere.
I didn't take them.
-Hi.
Are you calling me a liar?
What?
Why would you lie to me?
I don't know, you tell me.
Carlos, I don't understand.
Why do you say
I'm acting strangely?
That's what you told Julia
when you were alone, right?
That I'm acting strangely.
Isn't that what he said?
Come here! Come here!
Grab him, Julio!
Julio!
Grab him!
I've got him, I've got him!
Carlos, Carlos!
Listen to me!
Julia's cheating...
Let's see what this bastard
has to say for himself.
No!
I'm scared!
Isn't Julia kind of overreacting?
About what?
Not letting him talk and all that.
What's he gonna do, hypnotize us?
I don't know.
We could ask him why they're here,
what the fuck they're doing here...
That weird car Julia saw,
the one you drew...
Yeah.
Maybe he came in it
and he's got it parked somewhere.
-Don't you wanna see it?
-Yeah, sure I do.
If he could brainwash us
he'd have done it by now.
Take off his gag.
Wait.
Come here.
Maybe it is the real Angel.
So?
If it's Angel,
he's bound to go back
and tell Julia I didn't listen to her
and let him talk.
I'm not gonna let that bastard
give me away.
Just untie his hands and feet
and let him go.
Angel, if you are Angel...
I hope you understand,
okay?
I suggest you go
to the shopping malls
to the north.
There were no people around.
You know the way, right?
If you're not Angel...
Don't!
Don't take off the gag!
Turn around and beat it!
You got that?
Hi.
Isn't it Carlos' turn?
It's early.
I couldn't sleep.
Yeah.
He took out the gun?
You got that, motherfucker?
Well?
There are no bullets,
it's just in case.
It's not even loaded.
I got it from a sporting goods store
on my way over here.
He showed it to you?
No, I saw it in his pants.
I guess he didn't want to worry me
by taking it out.
I guess.
This is the first thing
we should have done.
I don't know why
I didn't think of it sooner.
He's impressive.
He knows what he's doing.
If he knew what he was doing
he'd have thrown you out as well.
At least now we know
we got rid of that freak.
Thanks for coming back.
Those are pages
from a city guide, right?
Yeah. It's the best view
of the city.
But they're printed
on both sides.
How did you manage that?
I took two guides from taxis
on the way here.
These are the quickest routes.
We'll have to make runs.
Julio, this is your apartment?
Yeah.
You'll need us to pick up
your things.
Yeah.
What's this line?
This is the area cut off
by the military.
The whole area under the ship
and these are the barricades
I mentioned.
Okay.
Right, first we'll go
through here to pick up
the generator for when the power
goes out, which it will.
Then we'll look for
a bookstore downtown.
We'll need manuals on
telecommunications, electronics,
stuff like that.
I'm making a list on the laptop.
Who goes with who?
Who stays home?
Nobody.
If we go, it's all three of us.
Why's that?
If Angel wasn't Angel,
what happened to the real Angel?
What if one of us gets left alone
and they switch us?
We stick together, no exceptions!
Damn!
What?
I found a two euro coin!
Are you sure?
-There are some swings over there.
-Yeah.
I wouldn't go near them.
When I went by there
I saw some nasty-looking guys.
Very dangerous.
Seriously, with guns and everything.
They tried to shoot me.
You couldn't pay me
to go over there.
A gas station.
With enough gasoline
we can make a bomb.
-But Carlos...
-There are other ways.
A bomb is a bit...
I'm not talking about killing anyone.
It's just in case
we need to scare someone.
We're not that far from home.
As long as we don't head that way
we're fine.
The water's been cut off.
-Already?
-Yeah.
We'll have to get more bottles.
Should I wake Carlos up?
No. Are there any more
in the kitchen?
-Yeah, I'll get them.
-No, I'll go.
When you walked by
in the towel earlier...
I saw your ass.
You did that on purpose, right?
What?
No way, you're joking.
How can you think that?
Come on, you know exactly
when your ass is in view.
Especially if there's a guy looking.
Well, you're less careful
if he's already seen it.
I've already seen it?
I thought we agreed
we didn't have sex.
We didn't, but you probably
saw my ass.
Right.
-Are you sure we didn't have sex?
-I don't know.
Do you know how the generator works?
It's still too dark.
Wait until your eyes adjust.
You'll see more.
That's it?
This is all we're gonna see?
What else do you wanna see?
Shit, the power's out.
Julia?
What?
Lower your voice, you'll wake him.
Are you still keeping watch?
Yeah.
Go back to bed.
Get some rest.
I'll never get back to sleep anyway.
Remind me when we go out tomorrow
to get a 300-foot extension lead
for the generator.
It's silent...
but it's better off
in the stairwell.
Or upstairs.
We'll find one that's...
Carlos, what...
''Tune UHF... We're still here.''
Damn!
Carlos?
I'm only asking you
for one thing.
When I ask you for the paper
don't take half an hour
to bring it.
Why don't you leave it
on the table?
I've told you a thousand times
I don't want any papers on it.
I can't be reading a piece of paper.
This isn't the news, this is war.
Then why keep asking for it?
When we're on the air.
I don't want it
when we're on the air.
We are on the air.
-We were, but you stopped.
-No.
-You stopped.
-No, we're still on...
This bozo claims to speak
for Madrid's refugees?
-You stopped, right?
-No, damn it!
More lights. We're not the only ones
with a generator.
We're not the only ones
watching this.
All those people listening to this guy
clueless to the danger we're all in...
Carlos, there's no need to exaggerate.
I'm being logical, Julio.
If they went to the trouble
of trying to fool us,
three schmucks in an apartment...
won't they try to trick
these people on TV?
I'm going to bed.
Me too, my head's killing me.
By the way,
I'll leave the laptop on
so you can check out my notes.
See you tomorrow.
...imposed by the government
due to this supposed threat.
We're convinced there might be...
Already?
Sorry.
-You know what we can do?
-What?
With the cans and the hose...
Since the heater isn't working,
we can run the hose out the window,
roll it up in a circle
and the sun will heat the water.
That would be nice.
I think I can pull it off.
Great.
-Goodnight.
Julio!
What's wrong?
Carlos is gone.
He must have gone out for something.
Isn't that weird? He's the one
who said we shouldn't separate.
-What do you mean?
-I don't know.
Did you bolt the door?
Julio, I'm scared.
Julia, this is insane.
It's not so weird
after what happened to Angel...
We might have exaggerated a bit
about Angel, don't you think?
What do you mean?
That we might have exaggerated a bit.
You lied about his car, didn't you?
No.
''Who'd steal that crate?''
you said.
How could you know it was a crate
if it wasn't parked there?
You mean you knew it was a lie
and you played along?
-No, I just realized.
-You're a fake!
Manipulator!
-Hypocrite!
-Liar!
Hello?
Somebody bolted the door.
Can you open the door?
Hello? Are you guys there?
Julia?
Hey, open up!
The door's bolted!
Carlos, where have you been?
I went to find an aerial.
Hey, you don't think...
Carlos, you said not to separate.
I didn't even leave the building.
I didn't...
You're right, I'm sorry.
We should have gone together.
Son of a bitch!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I can't ask you to let me in,
especially if I'm upset...
I'm sorry!
Carlos...
Actually, it's what he wanted.
To go out and save the world.
I don't know why he came back.
Not for me, I assure you.
He went to a lot of trouble
to get here.
And look how easy it was
to get rid of him.
Yeah.
You know what I mean.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Wanna have sex again?
JULIA'S FUCKING JULIO
Hey, Carlos!
Look!
Read the tennis balls!
Carlos, listen!
Julia's fucking Julio!
What the fuck?
Carlos, look outside!
Check it out!
JULIA'S FUCKING JULIO
Look what it says!
Julia's fucking Julio!
Has he always been a jerk?
What about you?
Have you always been a homewrecker?
What a bastard!
Where's Carlos?
He left! We're alone!
Where did he go?
Out to find stuff!
He'll be back.
Hey.
The first time I saw Angel,
when he came to see you,
he didn't ask about Carlos.
Isn't that strange?
You know he can't stand him.
I know, but...
wasn't he surprised
he wasn't with you?
Carlos hadn't been around for days.
Angel knew we were on the rocks.
You two were having problems?
Well, problems...
I didn't tell you?
I thought I told you.
We had a crisis.
Angel loves it when we fight.
Have you had many crises?
Of course we have.
We've been together since I was 19.
Julia, had you ever cheated on him
before?
I didn't cheat on him,
this isn't cheating.
This is...
It's more complicated.
No, I'd never cheated on him before.
It's working?
Hello?
Hi, how did you...
Yeah, Julio's here.
Okay.
-Okay, we're ready.
-Can you hear me?
Yes.
Hi, Julio.
Goddamn it! Hold on.
I can see you from here!
Get out of there right now!
Get out!
Okay, I'm back.
Quick, you guys can see Columbus
from where you are, right?
To the right.
Yeah, I think so.
Go out on the balcony and look.
I think there's an orange building
on the right.
Are you looking?
Yeah.
That was me.
Don't worry, the building was empty.
-But why?
-Take it easy.
Julio, listen to me.
I went to your building
in Hortaleza
and planted 4 bombs.
I can demolish it too.
What?
I need you to do something for me.
But I need a way to force you,
try to understand.
-I'm sorry.
-What do you want?
I'll tell you.
I need my books, notes, laptop...
Everything on the table
in the living room.
I need it badly.
I'm kind of in trouble.
What's wrong?
I took some stuff from the TV guys
and they're after me now.
Maybe I went too far
but I don't trust them.
-Carlos, please...
-Find somewhere safe
in your area to leave them.
I'll call you tomorrow at 8 sharp
and you can tell me where.
I have a remote detonator so I can
blow up your building anytime, okay?
And...
well...
Julia...
What is it?
I miss you.
I won't stop
until I regain your trust.
I'll blow those motherfuckers
back to their saucers if I have to...
Carlos!
You fucking asshole!
Bye.
Apparently we're not the only ones
he's threatened.
He's been seen causing trouble
at more than one shetler.
I mean shelter.
Several, in fact.
Read the paper.
If you see him,
and this is my personal opinion...
shoot to kill.
If you interrupt me again
while I'm talking
I'll kick your ass.
I swear I'll kick your ass.
Just read the paper.
I don't want to read it!
I'll stick it up my ass first!
You want me to stick it up my ass?
Yeah?
Fine, great.
Okay, you tape it so everyone
sees me stick this up my ass.
We're on the air.
-But I said to stop.
-No.
-Yes, I did.
-I said to stop.
-No.
-Yes, I did.
Good evening.
Unfortunately
sometimes danger appears...
What do we tell him when he calls?
Our facilities have been attacked
by an armed individual...
We'll tell him we jumped the gun.
He's dangerous, irrational...
That we were wrong
and to come back.
-This is what he looks like.
-Great!
You know what I'll tell him?
Julia's fucking Julio!
I'm going over there.
What do we do with him after?
What do you mean after?
I mean after we throw him out.
He's got nothing better to do
than bug us.
Who cares if we take away
his tennis ball machine?
He's got something much worse.
What?
All the time in the world.
I know a place where he won't bug us
and Carlos won't hear about it.
The garage where I work.
I have the keys.
We can take him there
and lock him inside.
Lock him in a garage?
It's big, it's where the floats are.
We'll bring him food and if he runs out
we'll bring him more.
I'm at the door about to...
Shit.
What's the matter?
He blocked it from the inside too.
Damn it.
I'll try and...
Julio! Julio!
Can you hear him screaming?
This ain't water!
Fuck! You son of a bitch!
If Carlos calls at 8
and I don't give him his stuff...
Julio, what is this?
Will he do it?
Will he demolish the building?
I think so.
You said you don't care, right?
I don't care about the apartment.
Julio,
what is this?
I've got an idea to get Angel
out of his building.
Damn, I should have put wheels on it.
-What time is it?
-Almost 8 o'clock.
He hasn't called yet?
He will soon.
Listen,
if this works and Carlos comes back,
what do we do with...
You know.
The simpler the better, right?
What?
Explain to him you believe
he's a human being,
that you know he's not an alien,
but that being separated and all this
made you think about your independence,
needing space,
and once you guys have broken up
we'll wait a while,
a couple of weeks,
and we'll act like we only just started
feeling something for each other.
Isn't two weeks long enough?
We'll play it by ear.
That's what you want, right?
To take it slowly.
-Right?
-Yeah.
Is something worrying you?
Why would I be worried?
I don't know.
That he won't believe us?
Carlos always believes me.
Julia...
Angel!
Angel, wake up!
Look down there, on the sidewalk!
What is that?
They're explosives.
Julio's been making them.
We can blow up your building
whenever we want.
We've prepared a demonstration
for you.
Julio, do it!
Carlos.
Hi. Is Julia there?
Carlos, go ahead and do it
if you have to.
Do what?
I didn't bring your laptop.
Don't worry about it.
Where's Julia?
Hold on a second.
Don't you want your stuff?
I did before, but not anymore.
Put Julia on.
Julia, what is this?
Here it comes...
Seriously, you can go ahead
and demolish
-the building.
-That's not necessary.
-Carlos, hold on.
-Seriously, listen to me.
Something happened.
You'll never doubt me again.
We have a technical problem.
Carlos.
Julia.
Prove to me you're Carlos
or I'll hang up.
What?
How long have you been
preparing this?
-You made a threat, right?
-Yeah, but...
Either make good or I'll hang up.
Are you fucking stupid or what?
Because the Carlos I know
never backs down.
I said, are you fucking stupid
or what?
Now will you listen to me?
That's my car, damn it!
Holy shit!
Look where my peaches were!
My car and my peaches!
You bomb people out of their homes
and you're also a thief!
Julio!
Yeah?
Hurry, come back!
Ricardo Rubin.
Gonzalo Prada.
Marta Navarro.
-Okay?
-Yeah.
What?
Those were from
the city of Pontevedra.
Now from Pontevedra province.
-He's taken the whole building.
-What?
Yesterday's explosion was to scare them,
to make them leave.
Rebeca Molinillo.
-Ours was just in case.
-He didn't get rid of that guy?
No, because he confessed
he's an infiltrator.
Pedro Pato.
Then Carlos told him to name
all the infiltrators in Spain.
Luis Angel Barreda.
He's just reading random names
to save his skin.
-Doesn't Carlos realize?
-Sara Castilla.
We'll tell him tomorrow.
Rodrigo Loro.
-Tell him what?
-I said we'll drive there tomorrow.
-What will we tell him?
-The truth.
Maria Chau.
What truth?
That we haven't been infiltrated,
we've been lying and I cheated on him.
No, hold on a second.
Julia, you didn't cheat on him.
This was something else.
Angel Numbella.
This is more complicated.
Maria Jose Carballo.
You want to tell him everything?
Eduardo Valdivia.
Okay, that's good.
Where's Angel?
I left him at the...
Him too?
-We'll do Galicia tomorrow at noon.
- But why?
Please write down
all the names on the list and share them
with as many people as you can.
We have to stop this.
If you know any of the people
mentioned,
take the necessary measures.
This is off, right?
Okay, then.
-Do you smoke?
-No.
What about you guys?
Don't worry, he'll understand.
I'll go get...
It's funny how your colleagues
gave you up so quickly.
They practically thanked me.
And how quick you were to confess.
Don't think I'm not aware of it.
I'll feel better
when my friends get here.
If you're holding anything back
we'll get it out of you.
She's as sharp as they get.
Did I tell you she spotted
one of your kind right away?
The day the ships came
she didn't even leave her apartment.
Only to help some stranger
in the street. How about that?
She's the person I admire most.
What sucks is I'm telling you this
instead of her.
I don't think I've ever told her.
It's the first thing I'll tell her
in the morning.
Julia wants to talk to you.
We both do.
What?
We're going home.
You can go back to your apartment.
What do you want to tell me?
We owe you an apology.
Out of nowhere?
What happened?
Don't tell me.
You screwed things up good, huh?
Did Carlos catch you two humping?
This is going to be good.
That's it, right?
Is that it? Is that it?
Is that it?
Hey, you're going the wrong way...
We're going somewhere
you won't bother us.
But didn't you say Julia...
I'll tell Julia I came here,
you got away,
I looked everywhere
and couldn't find you. Period.
What about Carlos?
Carlos, Carlos, Carlos!
Fuck Carlos!
Carlos has nothing to do with this.
I'm fucking in charge here
and I've had enough of you.
Shit.
The military has fenced off
the area right under the ship.
Apparently people have seen
some weird stuff out there.
I don't mean to scare you, but...
maybe they're already
doing something but in a way
we don't realize.
Maybe
they can fit in among us
without us realizing.
Shit!
What was I saying?
I was saying something.
Angel.
I'm sorry.
Please, forgive me.
What?
I didn't know...
-I didn't know...
-You didn't know what?
Please, let me go.
I'm begging you.
You'll never see me again.
I'll leave Madrid.
I've got a house in Cantabria.
I'll disappear.
Please, let me out of the car.
I won't tell anybody that you're a...
that you're a...
Well, you know.
-You're untied.
-What?
I didn't realize.
Here.
Anyway...
-You're leaving, right?
-Yeah.
You won't hurt me, right?
No.
Actually I'm thankful.
Why is that?
Because I've tried to get out
of this situation before and...
it's really tough.
What is?
Not having the balls to leave
when you know for sure
nobody wants you.
Right...
Here, take this.
I don't want it.
That means...
everything you've done...
you did it all for her?
Yeah.
Like you.
Yeah, but there's no comparison...
Hi, it's me.
Sorry, I set this up
because I didn't want to wake you.
I understand you wanting
to come clean about everything
and tell everybody, okay?
But I don't know...
I was thinking...
and I came up with one more lie.
Freeze!
Hi.
What were you doing in there?
I...
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry about?
-Where's Julia?
-She's fine, at her place.
But...
Carlos.
I came to apologize.
Apologize?
For actually being a...
You know.
I promise you I meant well.
I was gonna leave, take my...
machine and leave.
You wouldn't let me, remember?
But after that I thought,
''You'll never be this close again.''
You know how boring
my life is up there?
Wait, wait, wait!
That thing over there is yours?
Yeah.
I saw it.
It drove right past. I described it
and this looks a lot like it.
That weird car Julia saw,
the one you drew...
Yeah.
Maybe he came in it
and he's got it parked somewhere.
-There are some swings over there.
-Yeah.
You couldn't pay me
to go over there.
You had it parked by the swings.
-Son of a bitch!
-Carlos!
What I'm most sorry about
is you leaving.
Actually, we got rid of you.
It was me, Julia was against it.
I bolted the door and convinced her
not to open it.
But why?
Your notes, Carlos.
Your books, all that information.
I was dying to get my hands on it
without raising suspicion.
I was sick and tired of pretending.
-That's why you did it?
-I swear.
That's why you kept it.
That's right.
And that's why you didn't care
if I demolished your building.
You gave me a random address.
Exactly.
I only wanted to learn about you.
When I go back they probably
won't even ask what I did.
They might not even know I came down.
Almost nobody does.
No?
Well, maybe to take a stroll,
like I was doing when I blacked out.
But hardly anyone.
Do the ones on the ship know
what I've been saying on TV?
If the guy on TV were one of us
they would have rescued him.
They don't give a shit.
Damn.
What I did to that poor guy...
I've got him there.
Why did you leave the apartment?
Julia realized you were one of them,
didn't she?
Actually she never believed
you were one of us.
Is she by herself right now?
Then there was Angel...
I don't wanna hear about that jerk.
Here, let me. I'll handle it.
-This is the key?
-Yeah.
He's in a small room by the set.
I'll clear things up for him.
Hey!
Why are you here?
Yeah, with the ships and all that.
There's no reason.
What?
You came for the hell of it?
We extraterrestrials are like that.
If my plan works,
Carlos will be back anytime.
So erase this tape right away.
And that's all.
Actually, it's not.
There's something
I want to tell you.
I came close to saying it
many times but I thought
it might sound too...
forced,
too untimely,
too fake.
I'm not saying it won't sound fake now,
but I have to say it.
I love you.
How did you tape it?
What do you mean?
In a single shot or did you edit it?
A single shot.
I turned on the camera and said it.
You didn't write it down first?
It just came out?
Yeah.
It's not so hard, is it?
If I don't have it on paper
in front of me...
I butcher it every time.